<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5 - Create ​​bundles of products]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cross-selling & Product Bundles]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/cross-selling-product-bundles/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Allow the purchase of combinations of products with or without a discount, in one click  Would you like to increase your average shopping cart and at the same time, allow your customers to save money if they purchase several products simultaneously? It is now possible thanks to&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;!  Without waiting any longer, you can create packs of products that can be purchased in one click, without worrying about stock or their combinations.  A precious additional sales tool  Accompany your customers in their buying process, by offering them&nbsp;packs of coherent products&nbsp;that you will have predefined, just as the salesman in a real shop would do. Such as for example: this fantastic camera, memory card and tripod. You know that this selection is appropriate and that it will appeal to your customers.  Or you could even use your best-sellers, by adding them to those that are less visible, to allow your customers to discover them.  Your packs will need to be made up of 2 products minimum, the number is unlimited. Push the quantity per product, choose the combinations of your choice, there are multiple options allowing you to multiply the possibilities.  Would you like to reserve the purchase of a product within a pack? That is also possible! You will therefore be able&nbsp;to offer a free product&nbsp;if it is purchased as part of a pack. The possibilities are infinite!  Integrated assistant  It isn&#39;t always obvious deciding which products should be offered within a pack. Here again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution to the problem. When creating your pack, our module will supply you with strategic information, like the number of products sold or their available stock. There is also an integrated&nbsp;dynamic price simulator&nbsp;for your pack, to help you see more clearly when creating your business transaction, without you harming your profit margin.  Remain the maestro of combinations  One of the products that you have added to your pack is available in several colors, but you don&#39;t want to offer them all in this set? Advanced Pack&nbsp;will allow you to do this.  You will also have the possibility of predefining a combination by default, for each of the products of your pack, even if it&#39;s different to the one defined in your catalog.  Your customers will then be able to&nbsp;personalise their selection&nbsp;amongst the characteristics that you will have chosen to integrate in the offer.  Business Incentive  Incentive is something that motivates your visitor to make a purchase The main aim is to convince more of your site visitors to finish their order and/or&nbsp;spend more money per transaction. Perhaps you have already tried, by offering free delivery over a certain amount of purchases, or to offer discounts on certain products or even to send discount vouchers? All of these methods work, but their range is limited, as these promotions are usually temporary due to their excessive cost! Stop looking, you have already found the solution !  To entice your customers,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will give you the choice of applying a discount when all the products in the shopping cart are ordered, thus encouraging the purchase of the whole pack.  3 possibilities are available:&nbsp;Offer a specific discount on&nbsp;each product&nbsp;in the packApply a general discount on&nbsp;the set of productsApply a&nbsp;fixed price, such as a psychological price, for example Advanced Pack&nbsp;will also be able to manage the discounts already applied to your products, allowing you to integrate them in the pack price, or on the contrary, to exclude them, in order to choose the predefined discount on the pack. This decision will be made even easier thanks to our&nbsp;clear and clean-looking interface, that will allow you to see the discounted products very easily.  You won&#39;t need to worry about the coherence of your prices anymore  Have you ever had to review all the prices in your catalog, to detect any possible incoherences and correct them? What would happen if you had to manually manage the repercussions of these changes in product pricing in your packs? This would represent a significant extra workload if if it&#39;s not anticipated within the choice of management solutions within your packs!  Once again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution.  By default, in the case where no reduction has been applied, the pack price is the sum of the products making it up. Should you need to modify the price of a product after having created the pack,&nbsp;the pack price will automatically be updated, and without you having to intervene.  In those cases where you will apply a discount to one or more products in an existing pack, and on condition you have authorized the&nbsp;promotional implications, the pack price will also be changed, showing your customers the discount that has been applied.  Is one of the products of your pack subject to an green-tax? No problem, it will automatically be reflected in the pack price and will be clearly stated, guaranteeing absolute&nbsp;respect for the legislation.  Regarding the management of your stock, everything has been automated!  For each pack ordered, the product stocks it contains will be&nbsp;automatically deducted. This way you will avoid the double management of stock or the frustration generated by sales rendered impossible, due to the bad assignation of quantities. Also, in the case where a product in a pack is out of stock, it will&nbsp;automatically be displayed as unavailable&nbsp;for purchase thanks to an availability warning system that is both elegant and modern.  For your customers, we have integrated a graphic and fun notification system, allowing the instant identification of stock shortages on combinations or products making up the pack.&nbsp;There&#39;s no chance of you receiving orders for products that are out of stock !  Highlight your packs and sell more  Once you have defined your pack, you will be able to configure it in the same way as you would a classic product. Everything is possible, such as assigning it customized images, classing it in the category of your choice,&nbsp;optimizing your SEO, writing a customized description, attributing it an EAN code or a specific reference, configuring its volume to calculate delivery costs, etc...  For those that are pressed for time, and in order to facilitate their marketing,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will automatically display all the photos of the products that make it up, as well as their descriptions, in the form of tabs. Your customers will be correctly informed, without leaving the page of your pack, and&nbsp;able to finalise their purchase in one click.  And that&#39;s not all... For more visibility, your packs will automatically be&nbsp;highlighted on their data sheets&nbsp;for those being sold in lots This way, you will encourage your customers to order the pack, rather than the product they were initially interested in. Essentially, this is&nbsp;cross-selling: an accessible method of&nbsp;increasing your average shopping cart&nbsp;!  We don&#39;t forget designers  From the beginning, we have integrated the fact that this module should be easily adapted by your web agency or designer/integrator. The module adapts itself perfectly to the default PrestaShop 1.5 and 1.6 themes, whilst allowing the most advanced graphic personalization.  A set of JavaScript templates and CSS style sheets are delivered as models with the module,&nbsp;to facilitate the integration process. Either yourself or your integrator will therefore be able to use all of the functionalities of the&nbsp;Advanced Pack 5&nbsp;engine, in order to present them in the graphic form that will best correspond with the general atmosphere of your online store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.6]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[289.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[194.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[http://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[http://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1048]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsshoptab]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Facebook Shop Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Products on Social Networks]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Set up a mini-Shop on your Facebook fan page. A mini-shop will appear in this tab, and will display your shops' products directly on this social network]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/product-social-networks/1048-facebook-shop-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1048.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Set up a mini-Shop on your Facebook fan page. A mini-shop will appear in this tab, and will display your shops' products directly on this social network.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[*** WINNER OF THE 2011 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  An effective way to boost your sales. Enjoy the power of your Facebook community to communicate about your shop and increase the number of visitors and orders on your PrestaShop store.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.  You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.6]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[69.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/766915-pprod/facebook-shop-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[http://medias2.prestastore.com/766915-pbig/facebook-shop-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Delivery Tracking]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Do you deliver with UPS, a company known for its speed and reliability?  With the UPS Tracking module, make your life even easier by tracking your UPS shipments directly from your Back-Office and impr]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/delivery-tracking/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Do you deliver with UPS, a company known for its speed and reliability?  With the UPS Tracking module, make your life even easier by tracking your UPS shipments directly from your Back-Office and improve customer&rsquo;s satisfaction by automatically sending update emails to your clients when their order status has changed.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Take advantage of the UPS Tracking module: &nbsp;Get advanced tracking for your shipments, step by step, straight from your Back OfficeImprove your customers&rsquo; overall purchasing experience by regularly informing them about their order status and delivery of their package&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.6]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[http://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[http://medias2.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1768]]></id><name><![CDATA[gmerchantcenter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Price Comparison]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/en/price-comparison/1768-google-merchant-center-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-EN&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[http://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1768.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Instantly boost your traffic ! Google Shopping and Adwords benefit from hundreds of millions of hits each month. Moreover this traffic is highly targeted and brings qualified visitors to your shopIncrease your sales and ROI: Because traffic is extremely targeted, Google Shopping and Google Adwords Shopping Campaigns provide you with one of the highest return on investment rates compared to other marketing channels and is very cost effectivePresent in over 23 countries as of today, Google Shopping is a fast track start for international expansionWith over 5000 copies sold, 350+ reviews and an average 4/5 rating, our Google Merchant Center module is hands down the most robust, accurate, powerful and complete module for Google Shopping.We also have extensive knowledge and experience on the ins and outs of Google&#39;s rather complex requirements, 